autos.com 2010-05-16

# Autos.com: The best autos rankings site to help you find your perfect car online

We at Autos.com, an Internet Brands website (the "Site"), are committed to safeguarding your privacy online, and have designed our business practices to safeguard your privacy. This privacy policy applies to your information that we collect and receive; it does not apply to practices of businesses that we do not own or control or to people we do not employ. At no time will we sell your information or release your personally-identifiable data without your permission. You can visit www.autos.com without revealing who you are or providing any personal information about yourself. 

Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you use our services. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. By using this Site, you agree to the terms of this privacy policy. 

This Site contains links to other sites. These include links to third-party sites that offer automobile resources and related products. If you visit another website through a link on our Site, please consult the privacy policy of the website you are visiting. Autos.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites that you may visit. 

**Browsing the Site**

If you browse through the Site without entering any personal data, we will gather and store certain information about your visit. This information does not identify you personally and cannot be linked back to you unless you decide at some point to identify yourself. If you are only browsing, we collect the following information: IP address, the type of browser and operating system used to access our Site, the date and time you access our Site, the pages you visit (click-through), and if you linked to our website from another website, the address of that website as well as additional information related to your visit. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer the Site. 

**Information Collected**

There will be times, such as when you communicate with us by e-mail, submit an application, request a quote, request special financing, enter a contest or sweepstakes, purchase a product, etc., when we will need to obtain personally identifiable information from you or about you. Such personally identifiable information may include your name, home address, residence information, employment information, e-mail address, telephone number, social security number, financial information, bankruptcy history, credit references, etc. Consumers who submit an application, request a quote or request special financing expressly authorize us and up to four (4) third party partners to contact them in connection with each application and/or request regardless of whether or not such consumer is listed on a "Do Not Call" list. 

At no time will we sell your personally-identifiable data without your permission. The information we receive about you or from you may be used by us or shared (including evaluating and obtaining financial products or services) by us with our corporate affiliates, agents, vendors and other third parties to help process your request or complete a transaction; to comply with any law, regulation, audit or court order; to help improve our website or the products or services we offer; for research; to better understand our customers' needs; to develop new offerings; and to alert you to new products and services (of us or our business associates) in which you may be interested. We may also combine information you provide us with information about you that is available to us internally or from other sources. We believe that knowing more about you can enable us to serve you better. 

We may also aggregate your personal information with others' information and prepare reports on site usage, purchase history or other factors for sale or distribution to others. Those reports are aggregated and include no personally identifying information. Finally, we may use your personal information to send you email or postal communications regarding products or services offered by us or by third parties with whom we have relationships in which we think you may be interested. We do not share, sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties for unknown reasons. You may at any time choose not to receive promotional emails from us by contacting us at [unsubscribe@Autos.com](mailto:unsubscribe@Autos.com). Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact you for the purpose of communicating information relating to Autos.com, as well as to facilitate, complete, or confirm any transaction that you may enter into or responding to your inquiry or request. 

If you prefer for us not to provide your name and email or postal address to third parties for direct marketing purposes, please contact us at [unsubscribe@Autos.com](mailto:unsubscribe@Autos.com). 

We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources: 

  * Information we receive from you on applications on our website or other forms; 
  * Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others; and 
  * Information about you we may receive from credit reporting agencies. 

We may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to financial institutions, dealership lender partners, local dealers and other third parties that provide financing referral services to explore financing options to process your credit request. 

We also may disclose non-public personal information about you to non-affiliated third parties as permitted by law. 

All information provided by consumers in any of the above-listed ways or otherwise may be used and disclosed as permitted in this Policy. 

Information submitted to us in connection with a financing request is used to transmit the request to third parties who may be in a position to respond to your request. We do not provide financing, but instead transmit those requests to third-party vendors for consideration. 

Federal law requires all financial institutions to obtain, verify and record information that identifies each person who opens an account. When you submit a financing application, your name, residential address, date of birth and social security number will be used to verify your identity. In addition, as part of the request process, we may verify the information you provide, or obtain omitted address or other contact information from third parties. 

**Cookies**

We may place "cookies" on your personal computer. "Cookies" are small identifiers sent from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive, similar to a license plate, that help us to recognize you if you visit our website again. Also, our Site uses cookies to track how you found our Site. Cookies are not designed to be used to get data from your hard drive, your e-mail or any other personal data about you. To protect your privacy we do not use cookies to store or transmit any personal information about you on the Internet. You can reject cookies by changing your browser settings. Please note, however, that if you reject our cookies it is possible that some web pages may not properly load, your access to certain information might be denied or you might have to enter information about yourself more than once. 

**Updating or deleting your information**

You may update or delete your information at any time prior to submitting any request to us. Once a request form is completed and submitted, you will not be able to change any of the information. Additionally, please be advised that once you have submitted your request and the information has been received by lender/brokers, dealers, etc. this information is no longer under our control. 

**Security**

We safeguard your personal data (e.g., credit card and finance application information) during electronic transmission from you to us using known encryption, security standards and procedures. We restrict access to non-public personal information about you only to those employees who need to know that information in order to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and other procedural safeguards to comply with applicable privacy laws to guard your nonpublic personal information. We also assess new technology for protecting sensitive customer information on an ongoing basis. However, if your information is forwarded to a dealership or other third party provider, your information will be transmitted according to the security and privacy policies of that dealership or third party provider whose privacy practices may differ from ours. Your information as shared with outside providers will become subject to those different privacy policies. 

Due to federal and state regulations, we are required to keep a copy of your information for a period of 3 years. Over this period, we will maintain all such data in a confidential and secure area that third parties will not be allowed to access. 

**Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit Autos.com. These companies use non-personally identifiable information regarding your visit to this website and other sites, such as the user IP address, pages viewed, date and time of your visit, and number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), to serve ads to you on this site and other sites that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Specifically, Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Autos.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this website and other websites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

In addition, we use clear GIFs or pixel tags to help manage our online advertising. These clear GIFs enable our ad serving company to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits Autos.com. This allows us to learn which banner ads bring users to this website. The information we collect and share through this technology is not personally identifiable. 

To learn more about these practice and your choices about not having this information used by these companies please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp). 

**Trademark and Copyright Information**

Everything on our website is copyrighted (unless otherwise noted) and may not be used except with our express written consent. Use of these images by you or other third parties is prohibited and may violate the copyright laws, trademark laws, privacy laws and other laws and regulations. Nothing contained on this Site may be construed as granting any license or right to use any of our trademarks or service marks without our prior written consent. 

**Contacting the Website**

Please be aware that we may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. If we do, we will update this Privacy Policy at our website, so be sure to check back here frequently. 

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or privacy policies, please feel free to e-mail your questions to us at [information@Autos.com](mailto:information@Autos.com). 

Autos.com 

**March 24, 2009**
